Unlocked. Unleashed.
The Lair is a horror, action film directed by Neil Marshall.
Royal Air Force pilot Lt.
Kate Sinclair is on her final flight mission when her jet is shot down over
one of the most dangerous rebel strongholds in Afghanistan.
She finds refuge in an abandoned underground bunker where deadly man-made creatures known as
Ravagers — half-human, half-alien, and hungry for human flesh — are awakened.
Capt. Kate Sinclair, played by Charlotte Kirk.
Sgt. Tom Hook, played by Jonathan Howard.
Major Roy Finch, played by Jamie Bamber.
Corp. Kip Wilks, played by Mark Strepan.
Kabir, played by Hadi Khanjanpour.
Sgt. Oswald Jones, played by Leon Ockenden.
The Lair is a 2022 British action horror film directed by Neil
Marshall and co-written with Charlotte Kirk.
The film explores themes of bunker, afghanistan,
afghanistan war (2001-2021), murder, creature.
The tone is dark.